// src/data/coloradoMountains.js
export default [
  { front: "Mt. Elbert", back: "Sawatch" },
  { front: "Pikes Peak", back: "Front" },
  { front: "Longs Peak", back: "Front" },
  { front: "Mt. Sneffels", back: "San Juan" },
  { front: "Capitol Peak", back: "Elk" },
  { front: "Quandary Peak", back: "Tenmile"},
  { front: "Mt. Sherman", back: "Mosquito"},
  { front: "Mt. Massive", back: "Sawatch"},
  { front: "Mt. Harvard", back: "Sawatch"},
  { front: "Maroon Bells", back: "Elk"},
  { front: "Uncompahgre Peak", back: "San Juan"},
  { front: "Mt. Blue Sky", back: "Front"},
];
